We'll be right back.
Rescue our friends.
A bond among foes sworn with fists.
What in the world is this place?
An underground canal.
Hey, Luffy, you okay?
Water in my nose.
What did you expect would happen?
Careful!
Didn't see that one coming.
Oh man, this is getting exciting.
Hey, hey, hey, Granny!
It feels a lot like we're falling!
We're almost to the exit now!
Full speed ahead until we fly out of here!
What?
No way!
You're getting right!
All right, there it is!
Time to move out, men!
Let's charge ahead, join them, and get Frankie back!
Yeah!
Sodom!
Gomorrah!
Jump!
Straw hat!
The entire Frankie family thanks you for helping us!
We'll never forget it!
Fire the connection cannon!
Hey, nice job!
Pretty high-class bulls you got there!
Awesome!
Damn it!
Stupid bastards!
You idiot!
You gotta be more careful!
Thanks for help!
What a cheerful bunch of guys!
Hey, Monster Granite!
So is this the fastest that Rocket Man can go?
It's not very fast at all!
Just hold your horses!
Things will change once we hit the railway!
Railway?
Where is it?
I don't see it anywhere!
Ah, looks like it drifted a bit, huh?
Listen, I know these sea trains like the back of my hand!
I'll find that railway, no problem!
Found ya!
Let's go!
Attention, this train will soon be on the railway!
Once we are our acceleration will increase exponentially!
Find something to hold on to so we can keep the injuries to a minimum!
A minimum will be injured regardless?
Do what you need to lose?
Robert's kilowatt!
Ah!
Damn, I missed it!
No worries, we're just getting started!
Listen, you! Behave yourself!
Whoa! That was close, Granny!
A little to the right! Yeah!
Don't you worry, I'll get it right next time, you'll see!
Huh?
Timmy! Gundy!
No! I left you with iceberg!
How could this have happened?
Get out from there and come inside!
You'll be blown away out there!
We're fine, we're fine!
Whoa!
Timmy!
I'm gonna fall!
Whatever you do, don't let go!
I'm flying!
Wait! Hold on a second, okay?
Let me slow down!
Huh? Oh no!
No!
I forgot!
No brakes!
We can't stop!
Whoa, what the heck?
Hey, that kinda looks like fun!
Ha!
Look, it's the Straw Hat guy!
Hey!
Hurry!
Grab those two and bring them inside!
Once this train hits the railway, they'll be blown away!
Right!
Oh, oh, oh,OO!
Woah!
Oh, oh, what's this some old喜歡 engine?
Don't make him roar!
Look out of my way!
Uh, duas, duas, duas...
Put theracidmilesutrappin around!
ومöööööööööööööööööööööööööööööööööööööööfe
Yes! All right! They got onto the railway!
What? No way! Here, let me take a look!
Huh? Oh!
Yes, you're right! I see! I see!
Just what you'd expect from Miss Kokoro.
She's something else, isn't she?
Indeed! I must admit, for a while there, I wasn't sure what was going to happen.
I...
I know what you mean. With this storm and those waves, it must have been nearly impossible to find the railway!
Exactly! Quite right! I can't imagine what it must have been like...
For sure! For sure! Just look at...
Don't mind if I do! Yes, I see!
Say something else, all right!
Yes, no doubt! Hey, listen! Don't you think we should let Iceberg know what's going on?
Absolutely! I bet the old guy's worried himself sick about all of this!
Right! One of us should tell him then!
Rock!
Paper!
One of us should now.
Hey, there's no need to trouble yourself over him, either.
If he can survive being hit by a sea train, then I'm sure he'll be okay.
So, did you hear the news?
They're talking about it all over.
Tom's violent apprentice Cuddy Flan is dead.
He was hit by the sea train.
Iceberg, listen. I know you can do it.
You're the first apprentice of Tom, the greatest shipwright the world has ever known.
If anybody can do it, you can.
Hey, Kokoro. One of these days, let's share a drink. You know, when we actually have something to drink to.
Yeah.
Tom, I won't let you down. I'll watch over your dreams. I'll protect everything. Not only this town, but these blueprints as well.
Hmm?
There's a visitor, sir. He said he's a friend from years back. Do you know anyone named Cuddy Flan?
Frankie?
Shall I show him in, sir?
No. Turn him away.
You sure picked a roundabout way of meeting me.
Well, maybe. But anyway, what's up with that strange-looking body of yours?
Screw you! The sea train mangled my body, so in order to stay alive, I rebuilt it using some iron scraps.
But that's not the issue! I've heard that your company's been contracted to build ships for the world government!
I won't tolerate you doing anything to help them! How could you? They took Tom away!
And the weapons that caused the whole incident? Have you forgotten who made those?
I'm sure you have plenty of things you want to say to me, but I have a few as well.
I still haven't forgiven you. Four years isn't nearly enough time for that.
I'm surprised you even have the nerve to show your face around here after what happened.
What'd you say?
The government told me that you died in an accident on the railway. You never came back, so I believed it to be true.
Even if Tom forgave you, remember this. It doesn't mean for a second that I'm going to.
What's with all the secrecy? Something going on?
Huh? Hey, what are these? The blueprints for that old battleship?
Don't call yourself Cuddy Flam anymore.
Huh?
It's only a matter of time before the government targets me.
Now listen carefully. I want you to take these and leave this island, Frankie.
Why should I?
The Cuddy Flam from Tom's Workers is dead. As long as you don't use that name anymore, then there'll be no connection between us.
Additionally, if you leave the island, the whereabouts of the blueprints will vanish.
Hey, hold on a second. What happens if the government comes after you and you don't have them?
I've said what I came to say.
What the? Hey, Iceberg!
We shouldn't see each other again.
Wait, hold on. Listen to me. Do you want to end up the same way that Tom did? Hang on to those blueprints. If you're threatened and your life is in danger, just hand them over. And if you don't want to do that, you can burn them right before their eyes.
If you were me, would you do that? Tom had achieved so many wonderful things, but he gave up everything to keep these blueprints hidden from the world. As long as the risk remains that a woman named Nico Robin can figure out how to restore the weapon, then the world needs these blueprints to be able to fight back. If I continue to keep them with me, even if they threaten my life, I won't hand them over to the government.
Are you sure? You know me. What if I decide to build it? Do you really think that you can trust me?
I'm giving them to you. Doesn't that answer your question? We never change, do we? Every time we meet face to face, we yell and argue with each other. I won't forgive you. And you may feel the same way about me, too.
Frankie, I'm... I'm really... I'm so glad that you're still alive.
You listen to me! I'm not gonna leave this island! You got that ice for brains? I'm gonna do whatever the hell I want to do! You think I'm gonna do what you tell me? I'd rather die! Understand?
Damn it, Flunky! Why can't you get it through that thick head of yours? This is to protect the blueprints!
Shut it! It's you who doesn't get it! I'm not gonna leave this island, no matter what!
Why the hell am I thinking about ice for brains in a time like this?
Where is he? Where the hell is Iceberg?
He's dead.
I thought I was a goner!
You almost were! I said, if you don't come inside, you're gonna get blown away!
That speed was crazy!
Told ya!
He's right! That was rough!
Now, the light of a single one
I've found a feeling that I've seen
If I walk away, I'll run away
I'll run away from the future
I won't be able to do it
Once again, once again
È ll transporting
schneider
La heli
It opens
Puede
Mi
Ho
L'
Anti-
E
Look! That wave is freakin' huge! Amazing!
Ahh! If we don't do something, it's gonna swap Rocketman!
Everybody, hang on to something!
Are we gonna die?
All right, Captain. Let's do this!
Yeah!
Do this? What are you guys gonna do?
We're gonna fire a cannon!
On the next, One Piece!
Smash the wave! Luffy and Zoro use the strongest combo!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!